

DU CHI CONG

Frontend Developer

I'm Cong, I live in Hanoi, have 2 years of experience with projects outside of Japan, like writing web apps, open-source and web platforms. Right now I'm Frontend Developer but my target is Full-stack with JavaScript Reactjs, Vuejs).

Email
duconggpdg@gmail.com
Address
f Trung Van, To Huu, Nam Tu Lie
e m, Ha Noi
. Phone
s 0399557228
Date of birth
04-30-1994

duchicong.github.io

Link

Experience

Trung Van, To Huu, Nam Tu Liem, Ha Noi July 2019 - Present Frontend Developer

Current Company

- Backend, Frontend web development.
- Ensure that the website is built in accordance with the requirements of the customer.
- Perform maintenance and updates for existing client websites
- Change the code, software or graphics of existing pages

CT33 Pham Hung Building, Tu Liem, Hanoi January 2015 - November 2016 FullStark Web Developer

Vinamax VietNam Company

The leading company specializes in providing SEO standard website design services, SEO services, advertising services ...

- Position is FullStack PHP on NukeViet CMS platform
- Web design standard SEO, exchange and hand over the web with $\operatorname{customers}$

Skills

Dev tools: VSCode, Git, Postman, OS: Ubuntu, Window

UI/UX Design Material UI

Format code: ESlint, prettierr, jsConfig Seminar Optimize

Performance Markdown Team work JavaScript, ES6 PHP

Languages

English

Reading text, communication at work

Education

HTC Building, 236B & 238 Hoang Quoc Viet, North
Tu Liem, Hanoi
09/2018 - 05/2019

Fullstack PHP Web Developer

Aptech Education

Established in 2003, Bachkhoa-Aptech is one of the pioneers in training high-quality IT human resources for the country.

- Finish the course with excellent results

Km12 Cau Dien Street, Phuc Dien, North Tu Liem, Hanoi 2012 - 2015 Techology Infomation

Hanoi College of Technology

Certificate of excellence

Projects

My Resume Online

you can see more details about me, my goals, my career skills, professionalism and my coding style visually. If you accidentally lost my .pdf CV.

Technical: React JS, Material UI.

Due date: 2 months.

Source: https://duchicong.github.io

Project Management Foods

is a travel project that allows users to find and choose dishes that suit each taste, ensuring food safety factor for tourists coming to Japan. The project allows to link the chain of managed stores directly on the map, the user can choose, then it will direct customers to the store.

Technical: Laravel, React JS, AWS, Rest API Google Maps.

Due Date: 1 year

Position: Frontend Developer

Project Recruitment

is a recruitment project that can communicate with companies through chatbot, they can exchange information, salary, qualifications, set interview schedules ...

Technical: Laravel, Reactjs and AWS, socket.

Due Date: 4 months

Position: Frontend Developer

Project Management Restaurants

Restaurants are the management of chain stores and restaurants. in his roles as the manager and distributor operating the stores.

Technical: Project using Laravel, Vuejs and AWS.

Due date: 3 months.
Position: Fulltack.

Project Management Laws Documents

Laws is a law project that aims to administer documents and documents for lawyers before and after going to court.

Technical: Project using Laravel, Nuxtjs and AWS.

Due date: 3 months.
Position: Fullstack

My Burger Builder Practice projects from a Reactjs course allowing users to create orders and pay.

Technical: Reactjs.

Due date: 3 months.

Source: https://github.com/duchicong/burger-builder-react

My React-interactable snap points

drag and drop from point to point on the web just like swiping on mobile

Technical: Reactjs, package: react-interactable/noNative.

Due date: 2 days.

 $\textbf{Source:} \ \ https://codesandbox.io/s/react-interactable-snap-points-interactable-snap-point$

y6kmo

My Custom Pagination with Multiple Slide **Technical:** Reactjs, package: react-id-swiper.

Due date: 1 day.

Source: https://codesandbox.io/s/custom-pagination-with-multiple-

slide-nrc61